Rodrigo Soberon

Fullstack Developer

+54 911 6257 6133

Buenos Aires, Argentina

in /in/rodrigosoberona/

github.com/rodrigosoberon

rsdev.website

₽ PROFILE

I'm a bilingual Systems Analyst with more than 10 years of experience in business processes. Currently developing technologies in the Javascript and .Net ecosystems.

I successfully led projects with multicultural teams, fostering trust and motivation among members through direct participation in both planning and execution phases.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

09/2022 - present

Freelance

- Frontend web development
- · Online shops setup and customization
- Tutor of Backend course at Coderhouse
- Fullstack (JS and .Net) portfolio projects

Procurement Business Analyst

04/2021 - 08/2022

ALUAR | Aluminum Manufacturer 🛮

- Level 2 support for SAP MM and SRM's SUS Portal (Supplier Self Service)
- Maintenance and evolutionary improvements
- Integration with SAP BW module (Business Intelligence)

Project Manager | SAP Business Analyst

06/2015 - 10/2020

Chevron Co. 🗗

- Level 2 support for SAP MM module and JD Edwards SCM Module
- Projects led with offshore resources (India and Philippines) for tools linked to ERP core
- SAP notes implementation

Business Intelligence Analyst

02/2013 - 05/2015

Accenture Co. ra

- SAP BW (Business Intelligence) Business Analyst
- Data loading and Quality Assurance for daily production operations
- Functional specifications design and documentation
- · Batch data for testing creation

CERTIFICATES

Full Stack Developer 🗆

Coderhouse | Web development, Javascript, React JS and backend courses. (M.E.R.N. stack)

Data Science Bootcamp

Udemy | 365 Careers

The MERN Fullstack Guide

Udemy | by Academind

SAP MM Analyst 🛮

SAP Certified Application Associate - Procurement with SAP ERP 6.0 EhP7

EDUCATION

Systems Analyst

Universidad Abierta Interamericana

2022 | Buenos Aires, Argentina

P SKILLS

React JS

Express JS

Node JS

MongoDB

.Net (C#)

SQL (MS-SQL server)

Django (Python)

Flutter (Dart)



English (Proficient)

Spanish (Native)